

### Contact

Phone

+94-76-840-7950

**Email** 

tharun.varshanth.k@gmail.com

Address

No 02, Haputale Road, Diyathalawa, SriLanka

Linkdin

TharunVarshanth Krishnamoorthy

Github

Tharunvarshanth

Portfolio

# **Programming** Languages

Java

JavaScript

• Go

TypeScript

Python

• SQL

Dart

• C

### Databases

- MySQL
- Mongo
- PostgreSQL

# Tharun Varshanth Krishnamoorthy

Software Engineer at Daraz

As a highly skilled and experienced software engineer and full-stack developer, bring strong background in web and mobile to the table. I am confident that my dedication to the experience, and commitment to fostering an engaging learning environment align with the requirements of this position. I am confident that my qualifications and enthusiasm make me an excellent candidate for this role

# **Education**

**B.SC(Hons)** in Software Engineering

2019 Feb - 2023 June

University of Kelaniya | GPA 3.54

Cambridge ESOL Entry Level Certificate

ESOL International Entry 1

2013 | Result : Council of Europe Level A1

**Bandarawela Education Centre Computer Unit** 

2018 | Advanced Diploma In Computer Hardware

Results: B+

S.Thomas College, Bandarawela

2017 A/L | physical science stream

Results: 3B

# **Work Experience**

2023 March (Present)

**Daraz Financial Services Software Engineer** 

**1. KOKO** 

• Users can shop at their favorite retailers just got easier with a Python-based Decision engine system. They can split the cost of their purchases into 3 interest-free payments.

Vue js | Spring Boot | Mysql | Alibaba cloud | FastApi | **Android** 

#### 2. Daraz Seller Credit

• Giving the loan to the daraz sellers through sellers site Spring Boot (Pandora Boot) | Vue js

2021 Aug - 2023 March

### Mitra Innovations

Associate Software Engineer ( 2022 Feb - 2023 March )

- 1. Sillara Agri Tech
  - Sillara is an online market place located in SriLanka connecting B2B. Hotel, and restaurants can directly connect vegetable and grocery suppliers.

AWS | Cognito | React | aws serverless lambda .NET

### 2. Dygisec Triton

 Headquartered in Singapore, with operations in SriLanka and the US, Dygisec product company focused on Cloud Security. DygiSec is Cloud agentless, data driven cloud security solution

AWS | GO | Angular | Keycloak | Microservice | ngrx | Kong | Docker | Kubernetes

Intern Software Engineer ( 2021 Aug - 2022 Feb )

#### 1. Cellcard Mobile

Cambodian Telecoms company operating in 4G LTE.
Selfcare Mobile app available on android, ios, huawei android platforms. I worked on react native and android, ios huawei native level configurations.

React Native | aws server less lambda-node js | Bitrise

# **Volunteer Experience**

RealHack 4.0 | Software Engineering Students Association
2022 - 2023 | Organizing Committee

• Former Studpro 4.0 | IEEE SL Young Professionals 2021 - 2020 | Web Editor

# **Achievements**

OGoogle Hashcode Participation | 2021

Azure Cloud Skill Challenges Top 20 | 2021

Arimac Future Cast IOT Ideathon | 2021

### **Certification Courses**

#### **PEdx**

2020-Present

Applied Scrum for Agile Project Management AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials

#### **Q** Alison

2020 - 2021

**Operating Systems Courses** 

Diploma in Design Thinking

Scrum Immersion

### Referee

### **Deleema Fernando**

Senior Tech Lead at Lucytec

E-mail: deleemarf@gmail.com Mobile: +94-71-552-6825

# Frameworks & Technologies

- Spring boot
- React js
- Angular
- Vue Js
- Express Js
- Firebase
- Flutter
- Android
- Docker
- AWS
- React Native
- los
- Git
- Kubernetes

# Soft Skills

- Team Player
- Communication
- Problem Solver
- Time Management

### Interest

- Playing Cricket
- Traveling
- Volunteer Work
- Technology Blogging
- Continuous Learning
- Mentoring